Wow!
It feels so good!
Hey, do you think
I'll be able to do this, too?
Yeah. Of course you will.
You're my little brother.
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Discord"
"~To Become One~"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
We will now begin the seance.
"Client: Hitoshi"
I-Is that you, Dad?
Do you know who I am?
Oh, Hitoshi...
I never thought the day would come
when I got to see your face again...
Dad...
When did you learn
to speak Japanese so well?
Okay, logging out for a sec.
--Huh?
--Sorry, I'm not getting a very good signal.
Were you satisfied?
No! Please call him back!
Hey, please calm down.
Seances take a lot of concentration.
By the way, where is your father from?
New Jersey in America.
All foreign languages will be
auto-translated into Japanese.
This is an advanced technique
that does something-or-other
to the wavelength of the spirit's languages,
but there will not be an additional fee.
That's amazing! But I'm okay with English.
Now, then...
Oh, Hitoshi! How have you been?
It's Japanese... Well, whatever.
Dad, do you remember?
Remember how we used to
play ball when I was a kid?
And we did that one thing
that was popular on TV back then?
Show it to me one more time!
Dad?
Huh? What was that...
"Cheeseburger Tornado,"
the main character's special move
in "Junk Food Fighter Michael,"
the super popular show at the time.
Huh? What the heck?
Anyway, Hitoshi...
Cut to the chase and tell me what you want.
Dad...
If being cordial won't work, then screw it!
Yo, you shitty old man!
Tell me the password to the hidden safe!
I know there's a fortune in there!
Um, I think the password
was my birthday...
Don't give me that crap!
It's thirteen letters of the alphabet!
With that money,
I'll chill for the rest of my life!
Oh, now I remember!
The password is...
"GETAJOBYOUBUM"!
"Cheeseburger Tornado"
"Cheeseburger Tornado" This is one of Reigen's special
moves, where he uses his whole body like a spring
"Cheeseburger Tornado"
"Cheeseburger Tornado" and smashes his fist
into his opponent's face with a powerful spin.
And smashes his fist into his
opponent's face with a powerful spin.
Crap! The client's
consciousness logged out!
"Reception" "Limited Time Offer" "Get 3 evil spirit exorcisms
for the price of 21" Crap! The client's consciousness logged out!
"Reception” "Limited Time Offer" "Get 3
evil spirit exorcisms for the price of 2!"
"Reception” "Limited Time Offer" "Get 3 evil spirit
exorcisms for the price of 2" Did he pass out?
"Reception” "Limited Time Offer" "Get 3
evil spirit exorcisms for the price of 2!"
"Reception" "Limited Time Offer" "Get 3 evil spirit exorcisms
for the price of 21" Yeah... But, well, it was self-defense.
Yeah... But, well, it was self-defense.
Self-defense...
What? You look a bit pale.
If it's self-defense,
is it okay to shave off someone's hair,
rip off their clothes,
"Teru" is it okay to shave off
someone's hair, rip off their clothes,
"Teru"
"Teru" destroy their pride,
make them lose their friends,
destroy their pride,
and destroy the school they go to?
How can you do that much in self-defense?
There are times when
my psychic powers go out of control...
And it happens when
I'm unconscious, to boot.
I don't want these powers anymore.
If nothing else, they're of use to me.
And it's not just me.
Think of all of the clients
you helped with those powers.
Don't just focus on the negatives.
It's all about how you
use knives, remember?
Don't suppress yourself.
You're the one who holds the keys
to maximizing your potential.
Trust me.
You'll be fine.
Huh?
The shadow leader system?
Yeah. I completely lost to that
shadow leader named Hanazawa,
but the guy who beat him
is from Salt Middle School.
Someone that strong?
Yeah. We're gonna have him
be our shadow leader.
You're the one who caused the supernatural
incident at Black Vinegar Middle, right?
U-Um...
You're basically the only person
who could do that.
Oh, but according to the rumors...
There's a kid at Black Vinegar Middle
who easily throws people around, too.
Maybe he's an esper just like you...
And then you two met at Black Vinegar
Middle School and fought.
An esper battle!
That's what happened, right?
Twitch, twitch.
You don't want to talk about it?
That's enough for today, then.
But someday, you're definitely
going to tell me all about it.
Mob-kun?!
You mean that wasn't the work of aliens?
And that aside, there are
espers other than yourself?
Yes...
You can find them, right?
Huh? I've only met one other in my life.
That's strange. What about your master?
Ah...
Come to think of it, I don't sense
anything from my master.
But that's because his powers
are spiritual, not psychic.
"Psychic" But that's because his
powers are spiritual, not psychic.
But that's because his powers
are spiritual, not psychic.
"Spiritual" But that's because his
powers are spiritual, not psychic.
"Spiritual"
What kind of rule is that?
Well, whatever.
Let's go on a date after this.
Huh?
We're going to find other
telepathic people together!
And then take our first step
toward connecting with outer space!
But I'm not in the Telepathy Club.
Black Vinegar Middle School's
shadow leader?
I lost to him.
That guy had some nice muscles.
Th-Then who beat him?
It was someone from your club, right?
He's a gentleman who
usually dislikes violence.
Do not involve him in this. Begone.
Tch. Damn that Musashi...
--Hey.
--Huh? Y-Yes?
You were picked on by the guys from Black
Vinegar Middle School last week, weren't you?
That was all my fault. Sorry about that.
--Huh? What do you...
--Don't sweat the small stuff!
Sorry, Kageyama.
--Tenga-san's an idiot,
so he can't explain things proper--
--Shut up!
--Tenga-san's an idiot, so he can't explain things proper--
You asshole!
I'm talking to him. Stay out of it!
Well, then...
That will be all of the student council's
activities for this month.
Is that all right, President Kamuro?
Well...
"Salt Middle School Student Council President:
Kamuro Shinji"
"Salt Middle School Student Council President: Kamuro
Shinji" It's not bad, but we need something with more impact.
It's not bad, but we need
something with more impact.
Don't you think so,
first-year, Kageyama-kun?
You rank as one of
the smartest in the nation,
so I want to hear your opinion.
Right... In our school,
there are students known as delinquents.
"Pending Box"
"Pending Box" If the student
council could reprimand them,
"Pending Box"
"Pending Box" I think we'd be
able to create a peaceful school.
I think we'd be able
to create a peaceful school.
I see... A peaceful school, eh?
"Disciplining Delinquents”
That's great. Let's do that.
"Disciplining Delinquents” I have to make it
a comfortable environment for my brother...
I have to make it a comfortable
environment for my brother...
Kageyama-kun?
Thank goodness. I guess there was
a point in waiting around after all.
"Awakening Lab" "Mitsuura Kenji"
Here are my credentials.
Awakening Lab?
What do you think, Kageyama-kun?
Why not try to amplify your
psychic powers at my research facility?
He's got me confused with Nii-san.
Ah, Tome-san. That person--
What? Is he an esper?!
No, I just thought he had
a very unique hairstyle.
Oh, you're right.
Stop fooling around!
I'm being serious.
"Awakening Lab" "Mitsuura Kenji"
Oh, it's you, Kageyama.
Ah, Vice President Tokugawa.
Loitering, huh?
I guess even people like you
feel like doing that at times.
Like me? I'm just a normal middle school
student you can find anywhere.
Totally simple and normal.
You won't find a totally simple and normal
middle schooler anywhere on this planet.
But, for whatever reason, you want to
be one and are trying to act the part.
I'm not sure if I understand
what you're saying.
Despite having abilities that always
make you the center of attention,
you try to play the minor role
and let others have the spotlight.
Don't try to act like your brother.
Captain! Kageyama-kun is...
I'm fine...
I think you're starting
to build up some stamina!
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 4%"
"Mob Psycho 100"
Awakening Lab?
This place?
This is clearly just
a normal apartment complex--
"Fortress Seasoning" This is clearly
just a normal apartment complex--
"Fortress Seasoning"
Kageyama-kun!
You came!
There's no research facility here.
You lied to me.
Now, now, just come in.
Welcome...
...to the Awakening Lab!
What is this place?
I bought an apartment complex
and remodeled it.
I've hired the front runners
in neural science and engineering,
and we do research here.
The esper kids are on the floor above us.
They are?
Yeah, there are other people just like you.
There...
Another guy with a weird haircut?
That's an adult esper.
What is this feeling? It's kind of sickening.
Sorry, Tome-san. I was wrong.
Look, Mob-kun!
Isn't that hairstyle super weird?
Allow me to introduce them.
Real espers that the Mitsuura Group
worked hard to bring together!
First is Hoshino Takeshi-kun.
"Hoshino Takeshi"
I'm going all out!
He has psychokinetic powers!
Is that supposed to be amazing?
Next, we have Kurosaki Rei-san.
"Kurosaki Rei"
Her powers of clairvoyance allow her
to pick the one correct card out of ten!
Her efficiency rate is 62%!
Yay! I was right again!
That's it?
Next, we have Asahi Go-kun.
"Asahi Go"
Behold, my pyrokinesis!
Ignite!
Huh?
Ignite! Ignite!
Ig--There we go! Oh, it went out.
He uses pyrokinesis.
And is less useful than a 100-yen lighter...
The Shiratori brothers:
Daichi-kun and Kaito-kun.
"Shiratori" "Daichi" "Kaito" The Shiratori
brothers: Daichi-kun and Kaito-kun.
The Shiratori brothers:
Daichi-kun and Kaito-kun.
They're telepaths who can communicate
with each other, even when they're apart.
And less useful than email.
This is Kageyama Shigeo-kun.
Be nice to him.
Nice to meet you.
Did Mitsuura-san
do something to all of you?
Well, that's rather rude.
Don't worry. That old man is just
fascinated with psychic powers.
Huh?
I'm the son of a very wealthy family,
but I'm not anyone special.
I don't believe in doing anything to make
advancements in society or science.
I just want to become an esper myself.
So I made a research facility. That's all!
This is a childish pipe dream,
but if he's able to make
that happen, I'd be interested.
I always wanted to rise to my standards.
Oh, Shinji. You're finally home?
"Kamuro"
Student council again? Make sure
you don't fool around too much.
Nii-san was the
student council president, too.
But Takuya was also good in his studies.
Exactly. I'm embarrassed, Shinji.
You haven't even hit
a standardized score of 70 yet?
Are you really my younger brother?
You suck at violin, drawing,
calligraphy, and have no talent,
so you became the
student council president, right?
Then, you should have time to study.
How much are you going
to disappoint Mom and Dad?
Elites like--
Ah.
Ugh, you need to really
fix that habit of yours.
But it just bends on its own.
--What is it, a fart?
--Oh, stop that! We're eating dinner!
Shige, you need to be more like Ritsu.
Yeah.
Ritsu is much more talented than I am
and doesn't do anything weird.
Good morning, Kageyama-kun.
What's wrong, President?
Why did you call me here so early?
This is a girl's recorder bag.
What do you think is inside?
A girl's recorder.
Correct...
--President?
--It's long, so let's just take this off.
What have you been doing, President?
What am I doing?
Why, spring cleaning, Kageyama-kun.
Spring cleaning?
You said it yourself, didn't you?
"There is trash called
delinquents in our school.
The student council should
get rid of them."
I never said anything that extreme.
Please don't twist my words--
By the way, Kageyama-kun.
This is the desk of our school's
biggest piece of trash, Onigawara-kun.
A-Are you serious, President?
Why would an elite like you...
An elite?
That's just an imaginary persona
that someone labeled me with.
You've realized it, too, haven't you?
That the praise others lavish upon you
doesn't actually fit who you really are.
Come, help me, Kageyama-kun.
You got another perfect score on your test?
I'm
Ritsu is much more talented than I am
and doesn't do anything weird.
Don't try to act like your brother.
Even I...
Hey, do you think
I'll be able to do this, too?
Yeah.
Of course you will.
You're my little brother.
Really? Yay!
Huh?
All right, we made it to the goal.
You've got some good muscles
on you, Onigawara.
Damn it... You called me out early,
so I thought you were going to
tell me who the shadow leader is!
Remember that pain and
how good it feels, Onigawara.
The one you're looking for
is also fighting with himself.
So you should change, too.
Fine!
Bring it on!
There's been an incident!
Whoa, that's creepy!
--Hurry and do something about it! --Call the police!
--Can the student council do anything about it?
We're so grossed out, there's no way
we can take classes normally!
Now, now, calm down.
I promise that the student council
will find the culprit and stop them.
You open up Onigawara's desk.
We'll have to inspect everyone's belongings.
If they get caught like this,
they must be pretty stupid.
Oh, the teacher's not here yet?
I was about to ruin my record
of never being late or absent.
What's the matter, Onigawara-kun?
You seem out of breath.
What's Kamuro doing here?
What's going on?
Did something happen?
I found them.
They were all in Onigawara-san's desk.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you going through my desk?
So it was you, Onigawara-kun!
Huh? What are you--
Pervert.
Who the hell just said that?!
What the heck?
What exactly did you find in my desk?
We found all of the girls'
missing recorder pieces in your desk.
I'm sure you were going to lick them
when no one was looking...
You're such a pervert, Onigawara-kun.
What? Kamuro, don't make me punch you!
There's still time! Apologize!
Seriously, what is this?
Do I really look like someone who'd do that?
You are violent with other people.
That's reason enough not to trust you.
W-Wait! It wasn't me!
O-Oh, yeah! If I really wanted to lick them,
I would take them out of the school!
Only an idiot would leave them in his desk.
Well, you're an idiot, aren't you?
Stop being unreasonable, Kamuro!
There were some in his bag, too.
So you had taken a number of them home.
My school bag...
I left it wide open in my locker.
Kageyama-kun, you even put some
in his bag? You're all into this.
You bastard!
Stop snooping around my bag!
You're going to resort to violence?
--Poor Kageyama-kun!
--So gross.
--I have to disinfect mine.
--Give us back our recorders!
--You're terrible!
--You pervert!
Pervert! Pervert!
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Screw you all!
Run, everyone! The pervert's mad!
No... No! I didn't do it!
Isn't... Isn't there someone
who'll take my side?
I II...
I'll marry you when I get older, Tenga-kun.
D-Don't be stupid!
That's right... Mariko!
You believe me, don't you...?
Gross!
"Gross"
You're so gross, you perv!
On this day, after two years of hard work,
Onigawara Tenga's perfect
attendance record was broken.
What's the matter?
Don't be down. Everyone has bad days.
Did you see, Kageyama-kun?
Onigawara's face...
The despair of not being able
to solve something by fighting!
He's finished!
What am I doing?
--I'm going home.
--Huh?
I actually don't have psychic powers.
Oh, come on... Hey, wait!
Kageyama-kun?!
If it isn't Mob's little brother.
I see you're giving me
the cold shoulder as usual.
What are you wandering around
near my house for?
I got a request to exorcise a creepy ghost
that's been showing up in this area.
Want to help me out?
No. Unlike my brother,
I don't have any special powers.
Really? But you're Mob's little brother...
Why don't you exorcise this ghost yourself?
Aren't you a psychic?
Kageyama quit by throwing a spoon?
Not a towel?
He's got quite the sense of humor.
But as far as I can see,
he doesn't have much talent.
Actually... I'm not so sure about that.
Hm?
"Kageyama"
What's that?
It's not... a balloon?
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
After being hurt on a whim
something from somewhere
is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
"Yes n "No n
Ritsu continues to go wild
by pairing up with Dimple.
And then the gang leader
alliance makes its move.
Meanwhile, some scary people
try to make Mob buy a vase.
Both brothers are in huge trouble!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 7:
"Exaltation
- I've Obtained Loss~."
Illegal downloads?
You're going to be cursed.
"Exaltation” "~I've Obtained Loss~" illegal
downloads? You're going to be cursed.
"Exaltation"
"~I've Obtained Loss~"